<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OgreSpace</string>
    <string name="aboutogrespace">About OgreSpace</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">2249887752002229</string>
    <string name="google_map_api">AIzaSyCwFuBLNlN0azRUJ80g93QJ_RJLGRXVCCc</string>
    
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="ogre_space">
        <font color="#FFFFFF">OgreSpace</font>
    </string>
    <string name="about_ogre_space">
        <font color="#FFFFFF">About OgreSpace</font>
    </string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    
    <string name="rfp_as_paragraph_one">RFPGurus response is a team effort that requires non-stop communication and
        coordination between your organization and the client. Team work and system collaboration ensures success. We
        are striving to establish two-way visibility for boosting High Return on Investment (ROI) .We remove tiresome
        and lengthy processes and maximize the value of every single dollar you spend. When there’s competition, you
        always win. Don’t restrict the reach of your solicitations or make it hard for suppliers to submit responses.
    </string>
    <string name="rfp_as_paragraph_two">From locating opportunities to writing winning proposals, we have tools and
        resources that will make your business successful in the public-sector.
    </string>
    <string name="rfp_as_paragraph_three">RFPGurus provides a complete ALL-IN-ONE solution to tailor-build proposals for
        ANY/ALL RFPs for businesses within ALL industry sectors. Our ALL-IN-ONE PROPOSALS solution defines maps and
        designs the best proposals which are tailored specifically for YOUR business RFP requirements with the most
        competitive edge.
    </string>
    <string name="rfp_as_paragraph_four">Our teams of experts include Project Managers, Solution Architects, Business
        Specialists, Functional Analysts, Pricing Specialists, Technical Consultants, Software Engineers and Developers
        who carefully comb through the RFP that you have chosen. Once you have chosen the RFP, we prepare a Proposal
        which is best tailored according to your specific needs – all at the most affordable prices.
    </string>
    <string name="rfp_as_paragraph_five">Our visually stunning proposals include Slide Decks (Power Points, PDFs, Word
        documents), Technical Proposals (PDFs, Word Documents, Excel Books, PPTs), Mock Ups and Cost Sheets (Excel
        Books, PPTs, Word Documents &amp; PDFs).
    </string>
    <string name="rfp_as_paragraph_six">Please reach out to us using the CONTACT US form and let us know what RFP you
        would like us to build your Proposal for; We immediately assign a team of specialists to you who work FOR YOU
        until you are 100% satisfied with the Proposal that is 100% custom built according to your needs.
    </string>
    <string name="rfp_as_paragraph_seven">If you need help before, during, or after your purchase, then this is the
        place to be. Please use the contact details below for all your pre-sale and contact questions.

    </string>
    <string name="rfp_as_heading_two">The Tools to Win Government Business</string>
</resources>
